What I'm very concerned to use is
First of all, I want to know if deep seek creates images actually and the best resource to know that is to ask itself, right? So I ask it
Deep seek, let's say dear deep seek
Do you also generate images?
because I can't find any options
or buttons for that matter if you do
could you guide me on?
Creating images with you right and I send my command to see what we get
as you see it says I appreciate your question however, I'm purely text-based as you see and
I don't have the capability to generate images
yup, so as you see
Deep seek is incapable of
image generation, but as you see it's a
purely text-based
Generative AI chatbot